Guide to the Annual Reports 1973-2009 [Call #]
Eastern Connecticut State University, Publisher
- Series IV - 1995-1999
  - Academic Affairs: Communication, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication (3), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Academic Affairs: Education, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (3), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (4), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (5), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (6), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (7), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Affirmative Action, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Athletics, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Athletics (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Athletics (3), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Career and Experiential Education Services, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Counseling and Disability Services, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Data Center, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Data Center (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Facilities, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Facilities (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Finance and Administration, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Financial Aid, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Fiscal Affairs, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Health Service, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Housing and Residential Life, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Housing and Residential Life (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Housing and Residential Life (3), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Housing and Residential Life (4), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Institutional Advancement, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Institutional Advancement (2), 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - International and Exchange Program, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Planning and Institutional Research, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Planning and Institutional Research (2), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Personnel Administrative, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Personnel Administrative (2), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Public Safety, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Public Safety (2), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Public Safety (3), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Student Affairs, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Student Center, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Student Center (2), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - University Relations, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - University Relations (2), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - University Relations (3), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - University Relations (4), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - University Relations (5), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - University Relations (6), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - University Relations (7), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - University Relations (8), 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President of Academic Affairs, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Advisement, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grants Office, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Admissions and Enrollment Management, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Educational Excellence, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Academic Affairs: Chase Institute, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Access Services, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Academic Affairs: Library Services/Supplemental Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Academic Affairs: Media Services, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar's Office, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Academic Affairs: English Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Academic Affairs: History Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Academic Affairs: Political Science Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Academic Affairs: Philosophy Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Academic Affairs: Honors Program, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Science Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Academic Affairs: Writing Program, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Academic Affairs: Athletics, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grants-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Academic Affairs: Library-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Academic Affairs: Library-Resumes (2), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Academic Affairs: Library-Resumes (3), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Academic Affairs: Library-Resumes (4), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology-Resumes (2), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology-Resumes (3), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology-Resumes (4), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Academic Affairs: English-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Academic Affairs: English-Resumes (2), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Academic Affairs: English-Resumes (3), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Academic Affairs: English-Resumes (4), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts-Resumes (2), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts-Resumes (3), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Science-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology-Resumes (2), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology-Resumes (3), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology-Resumes (2), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology-Resumes (3), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Academic Affairs: Writing Program-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration- Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration- Resumes (2), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration- Resumes (3), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication- Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication- Resumes (2), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics-Resumes (2), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Academic Affairs: Education-Resumes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Academic Affairs: Education-Resumes (2), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Academic Affairs: Education-Resumes (3), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Academic Affairs: Education-Resumes (4), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Academic Affairs: Education-Resumes (5), 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Academic Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Administrative Affairs:, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Associate Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Akus Gallery/Gallery and Museum Services, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Environmental Health and Safety/Public Safety, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Facilities Management and Planning, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Fiscal Affairs, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Human Resources, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Information Systems, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Institutional Advancement, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Public Safety/Police Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - University Relations, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - University Relations-Resume, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - University Relations/Publication Sampling-Catalog, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - University Relations/Publication Sampling-, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - University Relations/Publication Sampling, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - University Relations/Publication Sampling, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - University Relations/Publication Sampling, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - University Relations/Publication Sampling, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - University Relations/Publication Sampling, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - University Relations/Publication Sampling Administrative Affairs: Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Division of Student Affairs, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Department of Career and, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Equity and Diversity, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Financial Aid/Veterans Affairs Office, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Student Center/Student Activities Office, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Health Services, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Counseling and Disability Services, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Unity Center, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Campus Judicial and New Student Orientation Programs, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 135)
- Series V - 2000-2004
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Academic Affairs: Modern and Classical Languages (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Sciences, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology- Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology-Resumes (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology-Resumes (3), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology-Resumes (4), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology-Resumes (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology-Resumes (3), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology-Resumes (4), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology-Resumes (5), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Academic Affairs: Social Work, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Academic Affairs: Honors Program, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Academic Affairs: Writing Program, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Education (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Education and, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration-Resumes (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration-Resumes (3), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration- Resumes (4), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration- Resumes (5), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication- Resumes (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Academic Affairs: Communication-Resumes (3), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics-Resumes (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Academic Affairs: Education, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (3), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (4), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Academic Affairs: Education-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Academic Affairs: Education-Resumes (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Academic Affairs: Education- Resumes (3), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Academic Affairs: Education- Resumes (4), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Administrative: Executive Vice President, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Athletics, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Athletics (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Athletics (3), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Athletics (4), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Budget and Fiscal Affairs, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Equity and Diversity, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Management and Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Finance and Administration, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Human Resources, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Information Systems, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Information Systems (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Information Systems (3), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Institutional Advancement, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Institutional Advancement (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Planning and Institutional Research, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Public Safety, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Public Safety (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Division of Student Affairs, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - University Relations, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President's Executive Summary, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President- Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grant's Office, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grant's Office-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Academic Affairs: Admissions and Enrollment, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Academic Affairs: Admissions and Enrollment-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Academic Affairs: Advisement Center- Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Academic Affairs: Akus Gallery, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Educational Excellence, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Educational Excellence (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Educational Excellence (3), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Academic Affairs: David Chase Enterprise, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Academic Affairs: Library, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (3), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (4), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (5), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (6), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (7), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (8), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (9), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (10), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Academic Affairs: Library-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Academic Affairs: Library-Resumes (2), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Academic Affairs: Library-Resumes (3), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Academic Affairs: Media Services, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Academic Affairs: Media Services-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar's Office, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar's Office-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Sciences, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Arts and Sciences-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (2), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (3), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology-Resumes (2), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology-Resumes (3), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Academic Affairs: English, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs: English (2), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Academic Affairs: English- Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs: English- Resumes (2), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Academic Affairs: English- Resumes (3), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs: English- Resumes (4), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Academic Affairs: English-Resumes (5), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts (2), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts- Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts Resumes (2), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Academic Affairs: Fine Arts Resume (3), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Academic Affairs: Visual Arts, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Academic Affairs: Visual Arts (2), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Academic Affairs: Visual Arts (3), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Academic Affairs: Visual Arts-Resumes, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Academic Affairs: Visual Arts-Resumes (2), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Academic Affairs: Visual Arts-Resumes (3), 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Academic Affairs: History/Philosophy/Political Science, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Academic Affairs: Vice President, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Academic Affairs: Dean of Arts and Sciences, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Academic Affairs: School of Continuing Ed., 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Advisement, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Academic Affairs: Academic Grants Office, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (1) - Summary, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (2) - Department, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (3) - Assessment/Performance, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (4) - Future Directions, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Academic Affairs: Biology (5) - Resumes, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Academic Affairs: Business Administration (3) -, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Academic Affairs: Center for Educational Excellence, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Academic Affairs: Chase Institute, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Academic Affairs: Communications (1) - Summary, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Academic Affairs: Communications (2) - Department, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 68)